{"status":"Success","data":[{"question":"\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d35\u0d3e\u0d37\u0d3f\u0d02\u0d17\u0d4d\u200c\u0d1f\u0d7a \u0d21\u0d3f \u0d38\u0d3f \u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28 \u0d2e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d02 \u0d06\u0d30\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d47\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d15\u0d30\u0d23\u0d02 \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d24\u0d4d? ","answer":"Mary Jackson "},{"question":"\u0d2e\u0d39\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d30 \u0d38\u0d7c\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d41\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d1a\u0d40\u0d2b\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d46\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d31\u0d3f \u0d06\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d2f \u0d35\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f? ","answer":"\u0d38\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1c\u0d2f\u0d4d\u200c \u0d15\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d7c "},{"question":"\u0d35\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d33\u0d3f \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d23\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f Drone mounted U I V sprayer \u0d09\u0d2a\u0d2f\u0d4b\u0d17\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02? ","answer":"\u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f "},{"question":"\u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d38\u0d2d \u0d1f\u0d3f \u0d35\u0d3f \u0d2f\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d38\u0d2d \u0d1f\u0d3f \u0d35\u0d3f \u0d2f\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d32\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d41 \u0d2a\u0d41\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d35\u0d30\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d? ","answer":"\u0d38\u0d7b\u0d38\u0d26\u0d4d \u0d1f\u0d3f \u0d35\u0d3f "},{"question":"2020\u0d7d \u0d28\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d3f \u0d26\u0d47\u0d36\u0d4d \u0d2e\u0d41\u0d16\u0d4d \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d40\u0d2f \u0d17\u0d57\u0d30\u0d35\u0d4d \u0d17\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d38\u0d2d \u0d2a\u0d41\u0d30\u0d38\u0d4d\u200c\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d02 \u0d28\u0d47\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d2a\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d? ","answer":"\u0d2e\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3e\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d47\u0d30\u0d3f (\u0d2e\u0d32\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d41\u0d31\u0d02 )"},{"question":"\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d46 \u0d38\u0d41\u0d30\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d32\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d0e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d15\u0d46 \u0d0e\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d7c \u0d1f\u0d3f \u0d38\u0d3f \u0d06\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d2a\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d24\u0d3f? ","answer":"Bus On Demand (BOND)"},{"question":"\u0d15\u0d4a\u0d24\u0d41\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d1c\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d2a\u0d15\u0d7c\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d35\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d27\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d33\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d35\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d2a\u0d28\u0d02 \u0d24\u0d1f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33 \u0d38\u0d7c\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d7c \u0d28\u0d1f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d06\u0d30\u0d4b\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d2c\u0d4b\u0d27\u0d35\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d30\u0d23 \u0d2a\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d1f\u0d3f? ","answer":"\u0d24\u0d4b\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d47\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d40\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d3e\u0d02 "},{"question":"2020\u0d7d \u0d15\u0d47\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d30 \u0d2a\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d \u0d2e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d32\u0d2f\u0d02 \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d16\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d26\u0d3f\u0d7b \u0d26\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d7d \u0d09\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d27\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d2f \u0d2a\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d36\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d40\u0d15\u0d30\u0d7a \u0d2a\u0d41\u0d30\u0d38\u0d4d\u200c\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d05\u0d7c\u0d39\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f \u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d1c\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d3e \u0d2a\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d ? ","answer":"\u0d24\u0d43\u0d36\u0d42\u0d7c (\u0d2c\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d\u200c \u0d2a\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d- \u0d2e\u0d41\u0d16\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d32 )"},{"question":"International day in support to victims of torture? ","answer":"June 26"},{"question":"2020 \u0d1c\u0d42\u0d23\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d15\u0d4b\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d21\u0d4d 19 \u0d2c\u0d3e\u0d27\u0d2f\u0d46 \u0d24\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d7c\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d05\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d23\u0d2e\u0d42\u0d7d \u0d15\u0d4b\u0d7a\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d38\u0d4d\u200c \u0d0e\u0d02 \u0d0e\u0d7d \u0d0e? ","answer":"Tamonash Ghosh "}],"code":"100"}
